Guide to the Washington State University Photographs, Subject File 1892-1999
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 2: Negatives
  - Subseries 2.1: Athletics
    - Football, 1968 (Box 52)
    - Football, 1970-1972 (Box 52)
    - Football Half Time (Box 52)
    - Football Present/Past Heroes, 1989 (Box 52)
    - Golf, 1960s (Box 52)
    - Gymnastics, 1950~ (Box 52)
    - High School Track (Box 52)
    - Ski Team (Box 52)
    - Swimming, 1925-1949 (Box 52)
    - Swimming, 1950~ (Box 52)
    - Tennis, 1950~ (Box 52)
    - Track: Individual and Team pictures, 1950-1959 (Box 52)
    - Track Meets, 1960 (Box 52)
    - Track Meets, 1961 (Box 52)
    - Wrestling, 1950- (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous Athletics and Activities (Box 53)
    - Women's Athletics, 1940- (Box 53)
  - Subseries 2.2: Campus
    - Campus Aerial Views (slides), 1893-1899 (Box 53)
    - Campus Aerial Views (slides), 1906-1910 (Box 53)
    - Campus Aerial Views (slides), 1911-1919 (Box 53)
    - Campus Aerial Views (slides), 1920-1929 (Box 53)
    - Campus Aerial Views (slides), 1930-1939 (Box 53)
    - Campus Aerial Views (slides), 1940-1949 (Box 53)
    - Campus Aerial Views (slides), 1950-1959 (Box 53)
    - Campus Aerial Views (slides), 1960-1969 (Box 53)
    - Campus Aerial Views (slides), 1970- (Box 53)
    - Campus Aerial Views- color negatives, 1984-1985 (Box 53)
    - Campus Aerial Views (slides), undated (Box 53)
    - Campus - Athletic Fields (Box 53)
    - Campus - Building Groups (Box 53)
    - Campus - Miscellaneous scene 1, 2, 3 (Box 54)
    - Campus - Silver Lake (Box 54)
    - Campus - Winter Scenes (Box 54)
  - Subseries 2.3: Classes
    - Miscellaneous (slides) (Box 54)
    - Nursing Ed. (slides) (Box 54)
    - Nursery School, 1975 (Box 54)
    - Physical Education: Men (Box 54)
    - Students in Classes/Classrooms (Box 54)
    - Students in Classrooms (slides) (Box 54)
  - Subseries 2.4: Commencement
    - Pre. 1947 (Box 55)
    - 1953 (Box 55)
    - 1957 (Box 55)
    - 1959 (Box 55)
    - 1960 (Box 55)
    - 1964 (Box 55)
    - 1967 (Box 55)
    - 1970 (Box 55)
    - 1975 (Box 55)
  - Subseries 2.5: Conferences
    - Agricultural (Box 55)
    - Education (Box 55)
    - N.S.F. Workshop, 1975 (Box 55)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 55)
  - Subseries 2.6: Equipment
    - Instruments (Box 55)
  - Subseries 2.7: Events
    - Ag. Awards and Banquets (Box 55)
    - Activity Round Up (Box 55)
    - Award Presentations (Box 55)
    - Dad's Day, 1958-1959 (Box 55)
    - Dad's Day, 1960-1962 (Box 55)
    - Dances (Box 55)
    - Elections (Box 55)
    - Harvest Ball and Harvest Queen (Box 55)
    - Homecoming: Queen, Dance, Rally (Box 55)
    - Junior Prom (Box 56)
    - Little International (Box 56)
    - May Fete/May Pole Dance (Box 56)
    - May Queen (Box 56)
    - Military Ball (Box 56)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 56)
    - Mother's Weekend (Box 56)
    - Parties and Picnics (Box 56)
    - Rallies (Box 56)
    - Registration (Box 56)
    - Sophomore Tolo (Box 56)
    - Woman's Day (Box 56)
  - Subseries 2.8: Exhibits
    - Campus: Ag., Demo. train, Diary, Art, etc. (Box 56)
  - Subseries 2.9: Experiment Stations
    - Dryland - Adams Branch (Box 56)
    - Exhibits and Fairs (Box 56)
    - Irrigation - Prosser (Box 56)
    - Western and Southwestern Washington (Box 56)
  - Subseries 2.10: Faculty
    - Armstrong, Cliff (Box 56)
    - A (Box 56)
    - B (Box 56)
    - C (Box 56)
    - D (Box 56)
    - E (Box 56)
    - F (Box 56)
    - Foote, William Wirt (Box 56)
    - French, Dr. and Mrs. C. Clement (Box 56)
    - G (Box 56)
    - H (Box 57)
    - I-J (Box 57)
    - K (Box 57)
    - L (Box 57)
    - M (Box 57)
    - N (Box 57)
    - O-P (Box 57)
    - R (Box 57)
    - S (Box 57)
    - T (Box 57)
    - U-V (Box 57)
    - W (Box 57)
    - Group Pictures (Box 57)
  - Subseries 2.11: Graduating Classes
    - 1900-1909 (Box 57)
    - 1921 (Box 57)
  - Subseries 2.12: Greek Letter Organizations
    - Events (Box 57)
    - Fraternities (Box 57)
  - Subseries 2.13: Laboratories
    - Anthropology: A Swan Relocation (Box 57)
    - Audiovisual Center (Box 57)
    - Broadcast and Recording (Box 57)
    - Easter Seals Research (Box 57)
    - Laboratory Work (Box 57)
    - Sciences (Box 57)
    - Veterinary (Box 57)
  - Subseries 2.14: Livestock
    - Cattle (Box 57)
    - Horses (Box 57)
  - Subseries 2.15: Organizations
    - Associated Students of the College of Agriculture (Box 58)
    - Cheerleaders (Box 58)
    - Cosmopolitan Club (Box 58)
    - Evergreen (Box 58)
    - Future Farmers of America (FFA) (Box 58)
    - Grey W (Box 58)
    - Hawaiian Club (Box 58)
    - KWSU-TV (Box 58)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 58)
    - Mortar Board (Box 58)
    - Spurs (Box 58)
  - Subseries 2.16: Performing Arts
    - Music (Box 58)
  - Subseries 2.17: Presidents
    - Compton, Wilson (Box 58)
    - French, C. Clement - April 1952 - 1966 (Box 58)
    - Terrell W. Glenn - 1967 - (Box 58)
  - Subseries 2.18: Regents
    - Brown, J.J. (Box 58)
    - Gose, T. P. (Box 58)
    - Neff, Lyle (Box 58)
    - Group Pictures (Box 58)
  - Subseries 2.19: ROTC
    - 1961-1962 (Box 58)
    - Air Force (Box 58)
    - Unidentified and Undated (Box 58)
  - Subseries 2.20: Staff Personnel
    - Guy Brislawn Retirement, 1966 (Box 58)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 58)
    - Unidentified (Box 58)
  - Subseries 2.21: Students
    - Studying (Box 58)
    - Men identified & dated, pre-1920 (Box 58)
    - Men unidentified, ca. 1940-1949 (Box 59)
    - Men identified, ca. 1950 (Box 59)
    - Women identified, pre-1939 (Box 59)
    - Women ca. 1940-1949 (Box 59)
    - Women ca. 1950 (Box 59)
    - Alumni (Box 59)
    - Alumni & Golden Grads (Box 59)
    - Groups, Ca. 1940 (Box 59)
    - Groups in Dormitories, 1959-1961 (Box 59)
    - Miscellaneous groups (Box 59)
    - Married (Box 59)
    - Pharmacy Students from 1946 Chinook (Box 59)
  - Subseries 2.22: Visitors to Campus
    - Dignitaries & Politicians (Box 59)
    - Lecturers (Box 59)
    - Musicians & Concerts (Box 59)
    - Theatre (Box 59)
  - Subseries 2.23: Veterinary Scholarship Awards
    - Veterinary Scholarship Awards (Box 59)